Finding aid for the Albert Kahn Associates records, 1825-2014
Bentley Historical Library
- Architectural Drawings
  - Job No. 1605-1657
    - Chrysler Corporation, Jefferson Avenue Plant, Reinforcing First Floor Switch Room Platform, Addition to Building 52-A Elevated Toilet Room, Transfer, Drilling, and Tapping Machines in Building 42, Job No. 1646-BK, BW, BZ, Detroit, Michigan, 1948-1950
      - Construction Drawings, Architectural, Structural, and Mechanical, 9 drawings (Map-case 43, Folder 11)
    - Chrysler Corporation, Jefferson Avenue Plant, Two Story Body Paint Building No. 41, Job No. 1646-CE, Detroit, Michigan, 1954-1955
      - Construction Drawings, Architectural, 38 drawings (Tube 96)
    - Chrysler Corporation, Jefferson Avenue Plant, Two Story Body Paint Building No. 41, Job No. 1646-CE, Detroit, Michigan, 1954-1955
      - Construction Drawings, Architectural, 38 drawings (Tube 97)
    - Chrysler Corporation, Jefferson Avenue Plant, Two Story Body Paint Building No. 41, Job No. 1646-CE, Detroit, Michigan, 1954-1955
      - Construction Drawings, Structural, 17 drawings (Map-case 44, Folder 1)
    - Chrysler Corporation, Jefferson Avenue Plant, Two Story Body Paint Building No. 41, Job No. 1646-CE, Detroit, Michigan, 1954-1955
      - Construction Drawings, Mechanical and Electrical, 61 drawings (Tube 98)
    - Chrysler Corporation, Jefferson Avenue Plant, Court Building 71, Job No. 1646-CG, Detroit, Michigan, 1954
      - Construction Drawings, Architectural, Structural, Mechanical, and Electrical, 32 drawings (Tube 99)
    - Chrysler Corporation, Jefferson Avenue Plant, Boiler House Addition, Job No. 1646-CH, Detroit, Michigan, 1954-1955
      - Construction Drawings, Architectural, Structural, Mechanical, and Electrical, 50 drawings (Map-case 44, Folder 3)
    - Chrysler Corporation, Jefferson Avenue Plant, Removal and Relocation of Second-Story Concrete Columns in Buildings 2, 2B and 3, Body Conveyor Housing on Roof of Buildings 20 and 33, Job No. 1646-CJ, CK, Detroit, Michigan, 1954-1955
      - Construction Drawings, Architectural, Structural, and Mechanical, 6 drawings (Tube 100)
    - Chrysler Corporation, Jefferson Avenue Plant, Machine Shop Alterations and Additions, Heat Treat Building Addition, Job No. 1646-D, G, Detroit, Michigan, 1936
      - Construction Drawings, Architectural, Structural, Mechanical, and Electrical, 19 drawings (Map-case 44, Folder 4)
    - Chrysler Corporation, Jefferson Avenue Plant, Warehouse Building Addition, Service Building, Job No. 1646-H, J, Detroit, Michigan, 1936
      - Construction Drawings, Architectural, Structural, Mechanical, and Electrical, 29 drawings (Map-case 44, Folder 5)
    - Chrysler Corporation, Jefferson Avenue Plant, Additions to North and South Ends of Machine Shop, Job No. 1646-K, Detroit, Michigan, 1937
      - Construction Drawings, Architectural, Structural, Mechanical, and Electrical, 21 drawings (Map-case 44, Folder 6)
    - Chrysler Corporation, Kercheval Avenue Plant, Warehouse Building Addition, Service Building Addition, Job No. 1646-M, O, Detroit, Michigan, 1937
      - Construction Drawings, Architectural, Structural, Mechanical, and Electrical, 29 drawings (Map-case 44, Folder 7)
    - Chrysler Corporation, Jefferson Avenue Plant, Warehouse Building No. 52 South Addition, Building No. 21 Extension, Building No. 21 Alterations, Monorail System for Warehouse Building, Job No. 1646-P, R, W, Z, Detroit, Michigan, 1937-1942
      - Construction Drawings, Architectural, Structural, Mechanical, and Electrical, 26 drawings (Map-case 44, Folder 8)
    - Imperial Distillers Products Corporation Rectifying Plant, Job No. 1650, East Jefferson Avenue and Connors Lane, Detroit, Michigan, ca. 1933
      - Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn Engineering Corporation
        - Architectural/Mechanical Drawings, undated; ink-on-linen drawings, 16x21 inches
          - Site Plan (1) (Map-case 31, Folder 6)
          - Basement Plan (2) (Map-case 31, Folder 6)
          - First Floor Plan (3) (Map-case 31, Folder 6)
          - Second Floor Plan (4) (Map-case 31, Folder 6)
          - Third Floor Plan (5) (Map-case 31, Folder 6)
          - Fourth Floor Plan (6) (Map-case 31, Folder 6)
          - Fifth Floor Plan (7) (Map-case 31, Folder 6)
          - Sixth Floor Plan (8) (Map-case 31, Folder 6)
          - Seventh Floor Plan (9) (Map-case 31, Folder 6)
          - Longitudinal Section (10) (Map-case 31, Folder 6)
          - Cross-Section (11) (Map-case 31, Folder 6)
          - Details of Boiler and Pump Connections, Gin Stills and Storage Tank (12) (Map-case 31, Folder 6)
    - Ford Motor Company "Century of Progress" Exposition Buildings, Job No. 1657, A, B and C, Chicago, Illinois, 1934
      - Exposition Building (Rotunda) (Job No. 1657)
        - Architectural Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects, 2/10/1934; Ink-on-linen drawings with pencil notations, 23-1/2x58-3/4 to 23-3/4x60 inches
          - Plot Plan (1), revised 2/27/1934 (Tube 27)
          - Foundation Plan (2), revised 2/27/1934 (Tube 27)
          - First Floor Plan (3), revised 4/20/1934 (Tube 27)
          - Balcony Plan (4), revised 3/1/1934 (Tube 27)
          - Roof Plan (5), revised 2/27/1934 (Tube 27)
          - East and West Elevations (6), revised 4/25/1934 (Tube 27)
          - North and South Elevations, Cross-Section on Line "A-A" and Longitudinal Section on Center Line (7), revised 2/27/1934 (Tube 27)
          - Details of Entrances (8), revised 2/27/1934 (Tube 27)
          - Typical Cross-Section thru' Main Building and Window Details (9), revised 2/27/1934 (Tube 27)
          - Sections and Details (10), revised 2/27/1934 (Tube 27)
          - Details of Stairs and Escalators (11), revised 2/27/1934 (Tube 27)
          - Plan of Lecture Hall, Wall Sections, Framing Details and Projection Room Details (12), revised 4/5/1934 (Tube 27)
          - Interior and Exterior Elevations of Court Doors and Windows and Details for Main Entrance and Entrance to Industrial Exhibit (13), revised 4/5/1934 (Tube 27)
          - Details of Writing Room and Women's Room and Section thru' Historical Exhibition (14), revised 4/5/1934 (Tube 27)
        - Structural Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects, Ink-on-vellum drawings with pencil notations, 28x56-1/2 inches
          - Roof Framing Plan (1-S), revised 2/28/1934 (Tube 28)
          - Balcony Framing Plan (2-S), 1/29/1934; revised 2/28/1934 (Tube 28)
          - Footing Plan, South Portion (3-S), 2/10/1934; revised 2/26/1934 (Tube 28)
          - Footing Plan, North Portion (4-S), 2/10/1934; revised 2/26/1934 (Tube 28)
          - Footing Plan for Museum (5-S), 2/20/1934; revised 2/26/1934; 20-1/2x30-1/4 inches (Tube 28)
          - Framing at Escalator (6-S), 3/20/1934; Pencil-on-linen drawing, 17x23-1/2 inches (Tube 28)
        - Mechanical/Electrical Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects and Engineers, Ink-on-linen drawings with pencil notations, 23-1/2x59-1/2 inches
          - Foundation Plan (1-M), 2/1934; revised 4/10/1934 (Tube 29)
          - Section at Foundry Exhaust (1-MX), 6/20/1934; Pencil-on-vellum drawing, 13-3/4x22 inches (Tube 29)
          - First Floor Plan (2-M), 2/21/1934; revised 4/10/1934 (Tube 29)
          - Balcony Floor Plan (3-M), 2/21/1934; revised 4/5/1934 (Tube 29)
          - Detail of Conductors at Columns Z-1 to Z-22 and Y-42 to Y-101 and Piping and Coil Arrangement (4-M), 2/1934; revised 4/5/1934 (Tube 29)
          - Roof Plan (5-M), 3/24/1934 (Tube 29)
          - East Elevation and Plan of Transformer Room No. 1 (6-M), 3/24/1934 (Tube 29)
          - North, South and West Elevations and Longitudinal and Cross-Sections (7-M), 3/24/1934 (Tube 29)
          - Plan and Section of Globe Pit in Historical Exhibit, Section thru' North End of Building and Details (8-M), 3/24/1934 (Tube 29)
          - Floor Plan of Lecture Hall, Ceiling Plan of Writing Room, Section thru' Historical Exhibit and Details (9-M), 2/21/1934; revised 3/24/1934 (Tube 29)
          - Riser Diagram of Switchboard No. 1 and Details of Switchboard Rooms No. 2 & 3 (10-M), 3/24/1934 (Tube 29)
          - Riser Diagram (Tube 29)
      - Roads of the World Exhibit at Exposition (Job No. 1657-A)
        - Architectural Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects, Pencil-on-tracing paper drawings
          - Site Plan (1), 4/21/1934; 19-1/4x34-3/4 inches (Map-case 13, Folder 10)
          - Details of Roads (2), 4/21/1934; 19x34-3/4 inches (Map-case 13, Folder 10)
          - Detail of V.8 to be Painted on Tarvia Track (3), 5/7/1934; 17-1/4x27-1/4 inches (Map-case 13, Folder 10)
          - Part Detail of Serpentine at Entrance to Shell (4), 5/10/1934; Pencil-on-vellum drawing, 13-1/2x25-3/4 inches (Map-case 13, Folder 10)
          - Elevations of China and Germany Signs (5), 5/14/1934; 11-3/4x24 inches (Map-case 13, Folder 10)
      - Orchestra Shell at Exposition (Job No. 1657-B)
        - Architectural Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc, Architects, 4/20/1934; Pencil and ink drawings on tracing paper
          - Site Plan (1), 18-3/4x27-1/4 inches (Map-case 13, Folder 10)
          - Elevations and Sections (2), 19x27-3/4 inches (Map-case 13, Folder 10)
          - Plans and Elevations (3), Ink and pencil drawing on vellum, 24-1/4x35-1/2 inches (Map-case 13, Folder 10)
          - Half Plan, Cross-Section and Section on Line "X-X" (4), revised 5/14/1934; Ink and pencil drawing on vellum, 23-3/4x34 inches (Map-case 13, Folder 10)
          - Details of Light Slot in Arch of Orchestra Shell (5), 5/9/1934; 24x31-1/2 inches (Map-case 13, Folder 10)
        - Structural Construction Drawing by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architect, 4/20/1934; Ink-on-vellum drawing, 23-3/4x34 inches
          - Half Elevation, Section and Connection Details (1-S) (Map-case 13, Folder 10)
      - Garage at Exposition (Job No. 1657-C)
        - Architectural Construction Drawing by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects, 4/12/1934; revised 4/20/1934; Pencil-on-tracing paper drawing, 16-1/2x36-3/4 inches
          - Site Plan, Floor Plan and Section "A-A" (1) (Map-case 13, Folder 10)
      - Exposition Building (Job No. 1657-D)
        - Structural Drawing by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects, 4/24/1934; Pencil and ink drawing on vellum, 18-3/4x27-3/4 inches
          - Details of Stack Support-Soy Bean Process (1-S) (Map-case 13, Folder 10)
  - Job No. 1706-1743
    - Carillon Tower (now Burton Memorial Tower), University of Michigan, Job No. 1706, Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1936
      - Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects
        - Architectural Drawings, 1/8/1936; Ink-on-linen drawings with blue ink revisions, 21-1/2x36 inches
          - Plot Plan (1), revised 7/24/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 5)
          - Basement and First Floor Plans (2), revised 4/27/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 5)
          - Second and Third Floor Plans (3), revised 4/27/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 5)
          - Seventh and Ninth Floor Plans and Details (4), revised 7/3/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 5)
          - Tenth Floor and Upper Part of Bell Chamber Plans and Details (5), revised 7/24/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 5)
          - Eleventh Floor and Roof Plans and Details (6), revised 7/3/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 5)
          - East and North Elevations (7), revised 3/4/1936; Original drawing and electrostatic print (Map-case 7, Folder 5)
          - Sections "AA" and "BB" (8), revised 3/4/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 5)
          - Elevation of Lower Floors and Details (9), revised 3/31/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 5)
          - Elevation of Upper Floors and Details (10), revised 3/31/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 5)
          - Elevations, Sections and Details (11), revised 7/3/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 5)
          - Revised Details for Steel Stair (12), 3/9/1936; revised 4/16/1936; Pencil and ink drawing on vellum, 16-1/4x22-1/2 inches (Map-case 7, Folder 5)
        - Structural Drawings, 1/8/1936; Pencil-on-vellum drawings with colored ink and pencil revisions, 21-1/2x34-1/2 inches, except as noted
          - First, Second and Typical Floor Framing Plans and Details (1-S) (Map-case 7, Folder 6)
          - Ninth Floor Framing Plan and Stairs Sections and Details (2-S) (Map-case 7, Folder 6)
          - Tenth Floor and Upper Level Bell Chamber Framing Plans and Details (3-S), revised 7/23/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 6)
          - Eleventh Floor and Roof Framing Plans and Details (4-S), revised 7/23/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 6)
          - Quarter Plan and Section "AA" (5-S), 6/24/1936; 22x33 inches (Map-case 7, Folder 6)
          - Detail of Enclosure over New Stairs to Tenth Floor (6-S), 7/24/1936; 15-1/4x22-1/4 inches (Map-case 7, Folder 6)
          - Plan at Eleventh Floor Stair Opening (7-S), 8/29/1936; 17x25-1/4 inches (Map-case 7, Folder 6)
          - Proposed Method of Hoisting Bells (100-S), 3/30/1936; 22-1/2x30-1/2 inches (Map-case 7, Folder 6)
        - Mechanical Drawings, 1/29/1936; Ink-on-linen drawings with pencil and blue ink revisions, 21-1/2x36 inches
          - Basement and First Floor Plans (1-M), revised 3/30/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 7)
          - Second and Third Floor Plans and Lighting Riser Diagram (2-M), revised 3/30/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 7)
          - Fourth and Firth Floor Plans (3-M), revised 3/30/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 7)
          - Sixth and Seventh Floor Plans (4-M), revised 3/30/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 7)
          - Eighth and Ninth Floor Plans (5-M), revised 7/24/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 7)
          - Heating Riser Diagram and Details (6-M), revised 5/21/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 7)
          - Lobby Heating System (100-M), 6/16/1936; Pencil-on-vellum drawing, 16-3/4x22-1/4 inches (Map-case 7, Folder 7)
      - Supplementary Construction Drawings of Tower (Job No. 1706-A)
        - Architectural Drawings, Pencil-on-vellum drawings, 23-1/2x33-3/4 to 24x34-1/2 inches
          - Basement and First Floor Plans and Column Reinforcing Schedule (1), 3/6/1936; revised 6/9/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 8)
          - Elevations of Concrete Walls up to Second Floor Line (2), 3/7/1936; revised 6/9/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 8)
          - Framing Plans for Second to Ninth Floors, Inclusive (3), 3/10/1936; revised 6/16/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 8)
          - North Elevation, Second to Tenth Floors (4), 3/11/1936; revised 6/25/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 8)
          - Plan of Tenth Floor and at Top of Circular Head Windows (5), 3/18/1936; revised 7/23/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 8)
          - Elevation of Concrete Structure above Tenth Floor and Details (6), 3/16/36; revised 8/1/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 8)
          - Eleventh Floor and Roof Framing [Plans] (7), 3/13/1936; revised 6/9/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 8)
          - Part East Elevation above Tenth Floor (8), 5/5/1936; revised 8/1/1936 (Map-case 7, Folder 8)
    - Burton Memorial Tower Renovation (formerly Carillon Tower), University of Michigan, Quinn Evans Architects, Job No. 1706-B, Ann Arbor, Michigan, 2000
      - Construction Drawings, Architectural, Structural, Mechanical, and Electrical, 77 drawings (Map-case 45, Folder 2)
    - Chrysler Corporation DeSoto Plant, Welfare and Employment Building, Job No. 1719-A, Wyoming Avenue, Detroit, Michigan, 1937
      - Construction Drawings
        - Architectural Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects, 4/20/1937; revised 5/15/1937 except as noted; pencil-on-linen drawings, 19x29 inches
          - Plot Plan and Details of Watchman's Room (1) (Map-case 31, Folder 7)
          - Foundation and Basement Plan (2) (Map-case 31, Folder 7)
          - Ground Floor Plan (3), revised 7/13/1937 (Map-case 31, Folder 7)
          - Roof Plan (4) (Map-case 31, Folder 7)
          - Elevations and Window and Door Sections (5) (Map-case 31, Folder 7)
          - Building Sections and Wall Details (6) (Map-case 31, Folder 7)
          - Details of Main Entrance (7) (Map-case 31, Folder 7)
          - Details of Vestibule and Toilets (8) (Map-case 31, Folder 7)
        - Structural Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects, pencil-on-vellum drawings, 19x28-1/2 inches
          - Steel Framing Plan (1-S), 4/20/1937; revised 5/15/1937 (Map-case 31, Folder 7)
          - First Floor Plan of Revision of Steel Framing (2-S), 6/2/1937 (Map-case 31, Folder 7)
        - Mechanical Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects & Engineers, 5/11/1937; ink-on-linen drawings, 19x29 inches, except as noted
          - Foundation and Basement Plan and Sections (1-M), revised 8/11/1937 (Map-case 31, Folder 7)
          - First Floor Plan and Details of Heating and Pump Connections (2-M), revised 10/14/1937 (Map-case 31, Folder 7)
          - Plan and Details of Proposed Revised Fan Room (3-M), 6/11/1937; pencil-on-vellum drawing, 18-1/2x28 inches (Map-case 31, Folder 7)
        - Electrical Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects & Engineers, 5/28/1937; revised 7/28/1937; ink-on-linen drawings, 19x30 inches
          - Plot Plan and Part Plan of Basement (1-E) (Map-case 31, Folder 7)
          - Ground Floor Plan (2-E) (Map-case 31, Folder 7)
    - Chrysler Corporation DeSoto Plant, Third-Story Addition, Job No. 1719-B, Wyoming Avenue, Detroit, Michigan, 1937
      - Construction Drawings
        - Architectural Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects, except as noted, 4/20/1937; pencil-on-vellum drawings, 28x48-3/4 inches, except as noted
          - Third Floor Plan (1), revised 6/3/1937 (Map-case 31, Folder 8)
          - Roof Plan and Details of Expansion Joint (2), revised 5/18/1937 (Map-case 31, Folder 8)
          - Elevations and Sections (3), revised 5/18/1937 (Map-case 31, Folder 8)
          - Sections and Typical Wall and Roof Details (4), revised 5/18/1937 (Map-case 31, Folder 8)
          - Third Floor Plans of Stair and Elevator Towers Nos. 3 & 5 and Sections (5) (Map-case 31, Folder 8)
          - Details for New Body Hoist on East Side of Building, Servicing 2nd & 3rd Floors (6), 5/12/1937; revised 6/3/1937 (Map-case 31, Folder 8)
          - Details of Fresh Air Intake and Present Roof Fresh Air Supply (7), 5/12/1937; revised 5/18/1937; 16-1/2x32-1/2 inches (Map-case 31, Folder 8)
          - Details of Revised Switchboard and Transformer Rooms (8), 6/1/1937; revised 6/4/1937; 13-1/2x31-1/4 inches (Map-case 31, Folder 8)
          - Plan of New Transformer Slab over First Floor Switch House (9), 7/16/1937; 17-3/4x23-1/2 inches (Map-case 31, Folder 8)
          - Details of Trenches in Elevator Pits (10), 7/31/1937; 12-1/2x24-1/4 inches (Map-case 31, Folder 8)
        - Structural Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects & Engineers, 4/20/1937; pencil-on-vellum drawings, 28x49 inches
          - Roof Framing Plan and Column Schedule (1-S), revised 7/8/1937 (Map-case 31, Folder 8)
          - Truss Details (2-S), revised 6/7/1937 (Map-case 31, Folder 8)
        - Mechanical Drawing by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects & Engineers, 4/26/1937; ink-on-linen drawings, 28x49 inches
          - Third Floor Plan (1-M), revised 7/6/1937 (Map-case 31, Folder 8)
        - Electrical Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects & Engineers, 28x49 inches
          - Third Floor Plan (1-E), 5/28/1937; ink-on-linen drawing (Map-case 31, Folder 8)
          - Details of New Transformer Bank and Switchboard Room (2-E), 5/29/1937; pencil-on-vellum drawing (Map-case 31, Folder 8)
    - Lady Esther Manufacturing Building, Job No. 1736-A, Clearing, Illinois, 1937-1938 and 1944
      - Construction Drawings
        - Architectural Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects, 7/31/1937; Ink-on-linen drawings with pencil and colored pencil notations, 25-3/4x40-3/4 inches
          - Plot Plan (1), revised 8/25/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 4)
          - Foundation Plan (2), revised 9/23/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 4)
          - First Floor Plan (3), revised 8/21/1944 (Map-case 18, Folder 4)
          - Balcony Floor Plan (4), revised 9/23/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 4)
          - Roof Plan (5), revised 8/25/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 4)
          - Elevations (6), revised 9/23/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 4)
          - Sections, Cross-Sections and Longitudinal Section (7), revised 8/25/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 4)
          - First Floor Plan and Section Showing Furred Ceilings (8), revised 8/31/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 4)
          - Balcony Plans at Lunch Room and at Offices (9), revised 8/25/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 4)
          - Detail of Main Entrance, Section "A-A" and Elevations of Lobby (10), revised 9/9/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 4)
          - Details of Main Entrance Door and Vestibule, Main Lobby and Pylon "A" (11), revised 9/23/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 4)
          - Typical East and West Wall Section and Details of Monitor Roof and Sashes (12), revised 8/25/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 4)
          - Sections and Stair Details (13), revised 8/31/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 4)
          - Details of Doors and Depressed Railroad Track (14), 8/25/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 4)
          - Interior Elevations and Details of Doors and Windows (15), revised 10/25/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 4)
          - Section "L-L" thru' Toilets and Details of Ladders over Monitors, Expansion Joints, Flashing in Gunite Walls, and Shower (16), revised 8/25/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 4)
          - Details of Scale Pits and Fan Platforms and Louvre Houses (17), revised 8/25/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 4)
          - Detail of Receiving Platform Partition and Miscellaneous Details (18), revised 8/25/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 4)
        - Structural Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects & Engineers, 7/7/1937; Pencil-on-vellum drawings, 23-1/2x40 inches
          - Roof Framing Plan, Sections and Material Schedule (1-S), revised 8/25/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 5)
          - Framing Details and Cross-Section (2-S), revised 8/25/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 5)
          - Balcony Framing Plan and Column and Footing Schedule (3-S), revised 9/24/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 5)
          - Details of Fan Platforms, Oil Tank Room, Fan and Pump Room and Powder Mixing Platforms (4-S), 7/31/1937; revised 9/24/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 5)
        - Mechanical Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects & Engineers, undated; Ink-on-linen drawings with pencil notations, 25-3/4x40-3/4 inches
          - Foundation Plan (1-M), revised 10/12/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 5)
          - First Floor Plan (2-M), revised 8/31/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 5)
          - Balcony Floor Plan (3-M), revised 8/31/1937 (Map-case 18, Folder 5)
          - First Floor Heating Plan and Details of Coil Connections (4-M) (Map-case 18, Folder 5)
          - First Floor Plan and Typical Arrangement of Radiators and Piping-Rouge Department (4-M-Sup), 12/30/1944; Ink and pencil drawing on vellum, 19-1/4x33 inches (Map-case 18, Folder 5)
          - Balcony Ventilation Plan (5-M) (Map-case 18, Folder 5)
          - Foundation, First Floor and Fan Room Plans-Office (6-M) (Map-case 18, Folder 5)
          - Foundation and First Floor Plans (7-M), 10/14/1937; Pencil-on-vellum drawing, 25x26-1/2 inches (Map-case 18, Folder 5)
          - New Location Detail of Toilet Exhaust Fan (8-M), 11/16/1937; Pencil drawing on tracing paper, 18x27 inches (Map-case 18, Folder 5)
          - Lobby Plan and Section "A-A" (9-M), 11/28/1938; Pencil-on-vellum drawing, 15-1/2x26-1/2 inches (Map-case 18, Folder 5)
          - First Floor Plan and Sections (10-M), Pencil-on-vellum drawing, 25x40-1/2 inches (Map-case 18, Folder 5)
          - First Floor Plan and Details (11-M), Pencil-on-vellum drawing, 25x40-1/2 inches (Map-case 18, Folder 5)
          - Balcony Sprinkler Plan (100-M) (Map-case 18, Folder 5)
          - Details of Fan Platform and Dust Collector Frame (17-P), 11/15/1937; Ink and pencil drawing on vellum, 23-1/4x33-1/4 inches (Map-case 18, Folder 5)